

PERSONAL INFO

952-917-9410

yanggloria91@gmail.com

Falcon Heights, MN

in linkedin.com/in/gloriayang91

SKILLS

// TECHNICAL

Microsoft Word | Expert

Powerpoint | Expert

Excel | Expert

Outlook | Expert

Mac & PC Systems | Expert

E-Commerce | Intermediate

// PROFESSIONAL

Leadership
Project Management
Event Coordinator
Client Support
Customer Service
Sales and Promotion
Copywriting

EDUCATION

BACHELORS OF SCIENCE
MAJOR: Marketing Communications
MINOR: International Studies
University of Wisconsin-River Falls
River Falls, WI
2014-2018

GLORIA Yang

MARKETING COMMUNICATIONS

PROFILE

Gloria is an active member of the community and a volunteer for organizations such as American Foundation for Suicide Prevention. Not only is she passionate about diversity and innovation, but she has over 5 years of experience in customer service with an emphasis in Marketing.

EXPERIENCE

COLLECTIONS SPECIALIST

TENNANT COMPANY | May 2022 - Recent

- Managing large portfolios that consists of over thousands of customer accounts
- Following up on past due invoices and organizing customer data by utilizing customer portals and SAP

CALL CENTER REPRESENTATIVE

TARGET | September 2021 - January 2022

- Efficiently and effectively handled incoming calls, online chats and emails with high quality and professionalism, while achieving performance standards
- Demonstrated excellent guest service skills, strong work ethic, critical thinking, and integrity by utilizing active listening and accurate usage of documentation in a timely manner

MARKETING ASSISTANT

XCEL ENERGY CENTER | November 2020 - February 2021

- Led creation and execution of product testing procedures and requirements while supporting and managing the EV Subscription Service Pilot launch
- Established CRM by responding to inquiries with direct engagement and providing customer service care through Xcel Energy's website
- Conducted data analysis to identify and report on EV home charging trends and tracked/reported work orders on Salesforce

STRATEGIC ACCOUNT & E-COMMERCE SPECIALIST

TCC MATERIALS | February 2020 - June 2020

- Managed the electronic interface related to item data management for Menards,
 Fastenal, Amazon, and all other E-commerce platforms
- Utilized InDesign, Photoshop, and Illustrator to assist with Amazon uploads and Menards branded web page

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

// CERTIFICATES

HOOTSUITE PLATFORM License 11463343 April 2018 - Present

ADMINISTRATIVE ASSISTANT DIPLOMA Minneapolis Business College April 2014

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH | Native/Bilingual HMONG | Limited Working Proficiency

HONORS & AWARDS

HIGHEST UNITS PER TRANSACTION HIGHEST SALES VOLUME Bebe October 2012

HIGH PERFORMANCE TEAMWORK
HIGHEST SALES VOLUME
HIGHEST AVERAGE DOLLARS PER
SALE
Bebe
October 2010

EXPERIENCE (CONTINUED)

CUSTOMER ACCOUNT REPRESENTATIVE

3M | October 2018 - October 2019

- Engaged as the primary liaison with 3M internal and external customers by communicating professionally through telephone and written correspondence
- Developed solutions by linking projects to business strategies and initiating actions that deliver successful results
- Applied knowledge and understanding of SAP Software Solutions to process orders and record all customer data

MARKETING INTERN

EAT, DRINK, DISH | June 2018 - December 2018

- Handled Facebook and Instagram account for Eat.Drink.Dish by monitoring Facebook analytics, creating hashtags, and leading Instagram stories at events while also taking over the official @eatdrinkdishmpls Instagram account
- Provided hands-on assistance with managing and overseeing events on the day of, including checking-in and welcoming guests, directing event set-up and newsletter sign-up, as well as communicating with team and vendors
- Increased ticket sales for Eat.Drink.Dish's "Faves-N-Maves" event up to 12%

SALES EXPERIENCE

VISUALS/SALES MANAGER

BEBE | August 2012 - June 2013

MID-SHIFT MANAGER

BEBE | December 2011 - January 2012

SALES ASSOCIATE

BEBE | September 2010 - December 2011

- Collaborated with sales team to plan the implementation and execution of all sales promotions, in-store marketing campaigns, and visual merchandising projects
- Oversaw day to day communications and service requests for all Bebe Stores located within the Twin Cities and developed relationships with clients face-to-face by providing products suitable to their needs
- Displayed knowledge of current competitors and industry trends within fashion, visual merchandising, and retail marketing by composing marketing research reports